Tanapat Chamted

Bangkok

☑ makufff.tanapat@gmail.com

4 098 018 0495

• makufff.dev

in Tanapat Chamted

 \bigcirc makufff

About me

I'm a student interested in AI/ML with experience applying Deep Learning and Machine Learning to projects in Computer Vision, image processing, NLP, and various AI Applications. I have expertise in developing software with React, Flutter, Python, and Node.js for web and mobile applications.

Education

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang

Jul 2024 - Present

BS in Information Technology

Experience

Sriyapai School

2020 - Present

Junior Web Developer

- $\circ\,$ Developed and deployed web application searches for the list of Grade 7 and Grade 10 students by applying React and SQL
- Developed and deployed web application about love experience website by applying React and SQL

Fridayz VPS 2024 - Present

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer

- Designed and developed static website using NextJS for front-end
- Designed and developing web application using NextJS for front-end also learning using Xen Orchestra to manage visual machine for back-end to building RESTful API, and PostgreSQL for the database. This application help customer who want to rent VPS can automatically build visual machine

V89 Technology Intern

Aug 2024 – Oct 2024

Computer Vision & LLM

- Implemented a deep learning model for object recognition
- o Compress and implement the YOLO model to run on the CPU
- Apply computer vision models to work on Web Applications using Docker and REST API
- Pioneered the development of AI project management systems using LLM , GraphRAG to support customer needs, enabling faster management of large-scale projects

Certificates & Awards

The Promotion of Academic Olympiad and Development of Science Education Foundation under the patronage of Her Royal Highness Princess Galyani Vadhana Krom Luang Naradhiwas Rajanagarindra Mar 2022 - Apr 2022

- o Computer Olympiad camp 1
- ∘ Tools Used: C , C++

THAILAND NEW GEN INVENTORS AWARD

2 Feb - 6 Feb

- $\circ\,$ Gold Medal 2023 with project Disease detection in durian from aerial photographs
- o Gold Medal 2024 with project Semiautomatic solar-powered water Surface garbage collecting machine

Sillapa 70th 16 - 20 Jan 2023

• Gold Medal with Software Computer Project Grade 10-12

National Software Contest 24th

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

- o Project Development scholarship 10,000 Baht
- o Join the final round of National Software Contest

EGAT for All Competition

5 Sep 2023 - 8 Sep 2023

 \circ 1st Runner-up 2023 (recieve 30,000 Baht)

SPU AI MINI Hackathon 2024

30 Jan 2024

o 1st Place (recieve 10,000 Baht)

Super AI Engineer Season 4

2 Feb 2024 - Present

AI HACKATHON Online (Practice) - Image Processing

 \circ Ranked 53th or Top 13% on the leaderboard competed among 423 competitors

AI HACKATHON Online (Practice) - Data Science and Big Data

• Ranked 7th or Top 2% on the leaderboard competed among 409 competitors

AI HACKATHON Online (Practice) - Signal Processing

 \circ Ranked 18th or Top 7% on the leaderboard competed among 265 competitors

AI HACKATHON Online (Practice) - Natural Language Processing

- \circ Ranked 1st or Top 1% on the leaderboard competed among 247 competitors
- $\circ\,$ Bronze Medal Notebook in Kaggle

AI HACKATHON Online (Practice) - Hybrid (Image + NER)

- \circ Ranked 10th or Top 6% on the leaderboard competed among 175 competitors
- o Bronze Medal Notebook in Kaggle

AI Mini-Hackathon Liver Lesions Detection Ultrasound

o 2nd Runner Up (Pangpuriye Team)

AI Mini-Hackathon Home Credit - Credit Risk Modeling

• 1st Place (Pangpuriye Team)

AI Hackathon Brain Motor Imagery Classification and Application

o 1st Place (Pangpurive Team)

Jump Thailand Hackathon 2024

8 Jul 2024

Final 15 Teams to Join Jump Thailand Hackathon, a nationwide hackathon for undergraduate students to
ideate and prototype solutions to improve the quality of life for persons with disabilities and older adults.
 Learn about understanding this population, prototyping, and the technologies offered by AIS

Hackathon Onsite : AI for Human Activity Recognition in Wellness Management

14 Jul 2024

o 1st Place (recieve 30,000 Baht)

Llama 3 Hackathon in LabLab.ai

19 - 21 Jul 2024

o Best Use of Together AI, winning \$2,500 in Together AI credits: Team: Alpaca 8b, Project: Flashboi

Projects

Image Captioning & Raspberry Pi

Project Repository

- Developed an electronic classroom where multiple users can simultaneously view and draw on a "chalk-board" with each person's edits synchronized
- $\circ\,$ Tools Used: Python , FastAPI , Hugging face

Camera Workflow With Adobe Lightroom

Project Repository

• This project is a script for automated photo editing using Adobe Lightroom plugins. The script allows for

automatic photo editing and uploads the edited images to Google Photos using the Google API

o Tools Used: Lua , Google API

Music2LeadSheet Project Repository

✓ Project Repository ✓

• This project is a web application where we can insert songs and the web application can generate a leadsheet by using the vocals

o Tools Used: Python , FastAPI , Huggingface

Object Detection Application

Project Repository

- This project is a cross-platform application that applies Object Detection to applications
- o Tools Used: Python , FastAPI , Huggingface , Dart , Flutter

Flashboi Project Repository 🗹

- Flashboi addresses the challenge of outdated and manual flashcard creation by utilizing cutting-edge AI, specifically Llama 3, to automatically generate high-quality, relevant flashcards from any PDF document. Our solution is designed for students, educators, and professionals who seek a more efficient and effective way to study and retain information. With Flashboi, users can easily convert their study materials into interactive flashcards, customize their learning experience, and track their progress through advanced analytics. Unique features include personalized study recommendations, seamless integration with educational platforms, and support for multiple languages, making Flashboi a versatile tool for learners worldwide.
- o Tools Used: Python , Together AI , lLama-index

Technologies

Languages: C++, C, Javascript, SQL, Python, Dart, Lua, BashScript